Guide to the David Wojnarowicz Papers ca. 1954-1992 MSS.092
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VIII: Audio [See also Accretions 2001], 149974
  - Subseries A: Access Copies, 214687
    - Ben Neill, Two Dances / Mainspring c. 1986 (Parts 1 and 2), ID: 092.0640; 223201 (Case 092.0640)
      Content description: Tracks [1] and [2] are believed to contain Ben Neill's album, Mainspring.
      [1]--00:11:41
      [2]--00:12:47
      Source: 092.0328
    - Ben Neill, Mainspring, c. 1988, The Living Room, Inc., New York, NY, ID: 092.0642; 223202 (Case 092.0642)
      Content description: Believed to be part of Ben Neill's album, Mainspring.
      Duration: 00:40:56
      Source: 092.0329
    - Evan Lurie, Happy? Here? With You? In Spain?, solo piano 2/85 Seltzer, ID: 092.0644; 223203 (Case 092.0644)
      Content description: Believed to be recording of Evan Lurie's album, Happy? Here? Now?
      Duration: 00:40:07
      Source: 092.0330
    - Evan Lurie, Pieces for Bandoneon, ID: 092.0646; 223204 (Case 092.0646)
      Content description: Believed to be a recording of Evan Lurie's album, Pieces for Bandoneon.
      Duration: 00:44:49
      Source: 092.0331
    - John Fekner, Dennis Lattman and Sasha Sumner c. 1986: 1) Final Concerto, 2) Oil Drum Mix; audiocassette Sony CHF 60, ID: 092.0648; 225846 (Case 092.0648)
      Duration: 00:24:32
      Source: 092.0332
    - Rough mix, Visitation, Tell Me Something Good; audiocassette (F-4-E) TDK D-C 60 (Parts 1 and 2), ID: 092.0650; 225847 (Case 092.0650)
      Duration: 00:20:27
      Source: 092.0333
    - 1985 - phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) TDK D 60 (Parts 1 and 2), ID: 092.0652; 225848 (Case 092.0652)
      Duration: 00:29:24
      Source: 092.0334
    - 1985 - phone message/ telephone '85; audiocassette (F-4-F) TDK D 60 (Parts 1 and 2), ID: 092.0654; 225849 (Case 092.0654)
      Duration: 00:29:48
      Source: 092.0335
    - 1987 - phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) TDK D 90 (Part 1 of 2), ID: 092.0656; 225850 (Case 092.0656)
      Duration: 00:42:46
      Source: 092.0336
    - 1987 - phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) TDK D 90 (Part 2 of 2), ID: 092.0658; 225851 (Case 092.0658)
      Duration: 00:37:29
    - 6/2/92 - phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) Certron LN 60 (Parts 1 and 2), June 2, 1992; ID: 092.0660; 225852 (Case 092.0660)
      Duration: 00:12:29
      Source: 092.0339
    - July 1992 - phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) Panasonic C 60 (Parts 1 and 2), ID: 092.0662; 225853 (Case 092.0662)
      Duration: 00:31:25
      Source: 092.0340
    - no date - "Time period of Pete's death" - Phone machine, phone message; audiocassette (F-1) TDK D 90 (Parts 1 and 2), ID: 092.0664; 225854 (Case 092.0664)
      Duration: 00:37:46
      Source: 092.0342
    - no date - phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) Certron LN 60, ID: 092.0666; 225855 (Case 092.0666)
      Duration: 00:09:09
      Source: 092.0343
    - no date - phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) TDK D 30 (Parts 1 and 2), ID: 092.0668; 225856 (Case 092.0668)
      Duration: 00:13:53
      Source: 092.0344
    - no date - phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) Sony CHF 90 (Part 1 of 2), ID: 092.0670; 225857 (Case 092.0670)
      TRT: 00:44:50
      Source: 092.0345
    - no date - phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) Sony CHF 90 (Part 2 of 2), ID: 092.0672; 225858 (Case 092.0672)
      Duration: 00:44:34
    - no date - phone message side A; audiocassette (F-4-F) Sony CHF 90 (Part 1 of 2), ID: 092.0674; 225859 (Case 092.0674)
      Source: 092.0346
    - no date - phone message side A; audiocassette (F-4-F) Sony CHF 90 (Part 2 of 2), ID: 092.0676; 225860 (Case 092.0676)
    - no date - phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) TDK D 90, ID: 092.0678; 225861 (Case 092.0678)
      Duration: 00:28:53
      Source: 092.0347
    - no date - phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) Sony C 60 (Parts 1 and 2), ID: 092.0680; 225862 (Case 092.0680)
      Duration: 00:32:17
      Source: 092.0348
    - no date - phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) Sony CHF 60 (Parts 1 and 2), ID: 092.0682; 225863 (Case 092.0682)
      Duration: 00:29:41
      Source: 092.0349
    - no date - phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) TDK D 90 (1 of 2), undated; ID: 092.0684; 229505; Format: CD-R Duration: 00:42:25 Original Format: 1/4" audiocassette Source: 092.0350 (Case 092.0684)
    - no date - phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) TDK D 90 (2 of 2), undated; ID: 092.0686; 229506; Format: CD-R Duration: 00:40:10 Original Format: 1/4" audiocassette Source: 092.0350 (Case 092.0686)
    - no date - phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) TDK D 90 (Parts 1 and 2), undated; ID: 092.0688; 229507; Format: CD-R Duration: [1]--00:39:28 [2]--00:38:32 Original Format: 1/4" audiocassette Source: 092.0351 (Case 092.0688)
    - no date - phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) TDK SA 90 (1 of 2), undated; ID: 092.0690; 229508; Format: CD-R Duration: 00:42:03 Original Format: 1/4" audiocassette Source: 092.0352 (Case 092.0690)
    - no date - phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) TDK SA 90 (2 of 2), undated; ID: 092.0692; 229509; Format: CD-R Duration: 00:47:07 Original Format: 1/4" audiocassette Source: 092.0352 (Case 092.0692)
    - Unidentified Tape: audiocassette Sony EF 60 (Parts 1 and 2) [Spanish Language Pop Music], undated; ID: 092.0694; 229510; Format: CD-R Duration: [1]--00:30:24 [2]--00:30:09 Original Format: 1/4" audiocassette Source: 092.0358 (Case 092.0694)
      Content Description: Recording of Spanish language pop music.
    - Unidentified Tape: audiocassette, Maxell C 60 [Band Rehearsal], undated; ID: 092.0696; 229511; Format: CD-R Duration: 00:24:47 Original Format: 1/4" audiocassette Source: 092.0359 (Case 092.0696)
      Content Description: Recording of band rehearsal with David Wojnarowicz sing-speaking, possibly for his band 3 Teens Kill 4.
    - Unidentified Tape: audiocassette, Maxell UD XLI 60 [Sound Collage Work and Phone Messages], undated; ID: 092.0698; 229512; Format: CD-R Duration: [1]--00:30:32 [2]--00:27:36 Original Format: 1/4" audiocassette Source: 092.0360 (Case 092.0698)
      Content Description: Recording with sound collage work featuring David Wojnarowicz's voice and phone messages.
    - -Breakdown Journal NYC- Jan.; audiocassette D-C 60, undated; 092.0223 (Box Digitized Access Copies, File 092.0223)
    - -David, John conversation, 12/31/80; audiocassette (F-4B) Scotch Dynarange, undated; 092.0228 (Box Digitized Access Copies, File 092.0228)
    - -David Wojnarowicz, Friday, on censorship; microcassette (F-4-A) Sony MC 60, undated; 092.0231 (Box Digitized Access Copies, File 092.0231)
    - -(May 16 1982) NYC Self Conversations, Peters Loft, (RE: Sex / J.P. / Confusions); audiocassette TDK D-C 60, 092.0272 (Box Digitized Access Copies, File 092.0272)
    - -Broken piano/musak/jack hammer/Rev. Swaggart Mix; audiocassette TDK D 60, undated; 092.0290 (Box Digitized Access Copies, File 092.0290)
    - -Bum Crash, Ship Horn, [Speed], Clocks, Firing Range, Chose to Stay & Fight; audiocassette (F-4-C) Ampex 60, undated, 092.0291 (Box Digitized Access Copies, File 092.0291)
    - -Fashion chit-chat, Queer dinner / Ready on the Right - Roll Back for El Salvadore Song; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D-C 60, undated; 092.0293 (Box Digitized Access Copies, File 092.0293)
    - l Object -Gunfire Brian's song, Brian's song / Bum crash, Traffic report, Louis session 2; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D-C 90, undated; 092.0294 (Box Digitized Access Copies, File 092.0294)
    - -Hunger, Siren Pulse Beat, Buzzer, Surf / Crickets, Birds, Pool, Road Movie, Alcholism, Hold-up Tape [+] 10 Second; audiocassette TDK D-C 60, undated; 092.0295 (Box Digitized Access Copies, File 092.0295)
    - -Windshield Wipers, [Buvsisles], Hut; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D-C 60, undated; 092.0296 (Box Digitized Access Copies, File 092.0296)
    - -KIDS; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D 120, undated; 092.0294 (Box Digitized Access Copies, File 092.0297)
    - -PRISON SEX, Sex Movie Music/Prison: Drums; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D 60, undated; 092.0298 (Box Digitized Access Copies, File 092.0298)
    - -Queer riot fragments; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D 90, undated; 092.0299 (Box Digitized Access Copies, File 092.0299)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      "Queer riot fragments" compromise a portion of Side 1; the rest of the tape consists of Calypso music.
    - -Sounds: Reagan Shooting / Down & Out in Paris & London, [Asteroids] - Galaxian; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D-C 60, undated; 092.0301 (Box Digitized Access Copies, File 092.0301)
    - -Garbage Truck in 14 St. Meat Market / Sex Movies; audiocassette TDK D 60, undated; 092.0304 (Box Digitized Access Copies, File 092.0304)
    - -Soundtape USA #3 / Plane Taking off N. Mexico, Spanish Movie (Black Cat Appears), Bed Rock City (Dino Barking), Water, etc.; audiocassette (F-4-C) Maxell LN 60, undated; 092.0306 (Box Digitized Access Copies, File 092.0306)
    - -Sound Tape #4 Oregon / Rodeo Party Oregon, Rodeo Party Keith; audiocassette (F-4-C) Maxell LN 60, undated; 092.0307 (Box Digitized Access Copies, File 092.0307)
    - -Soundtape #6; audiocassette (F-4-C) Realistic Supertape Gold 60, undated; 092.0308 (Box Digitized Access Copies, File 092.0308)
    - -Soundtape #8, Alligator Tour, Louisianna, Storm Static Commercials; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D 60, undated; 092.0309 (Box Digitized Access Copies, File 092.0309)
    - -Sound Tape 1985 USA / Elvis's Home Memphis, Approx. 20 min., Frogs in Swamp outside Jackson Mississippi, Train? '', Steps, etc.; audiocassette Maxell XLI-S 60, undated; 092.0310 (Box Digitized Access Copies, File 092.0310)
    - -Sound Tape, Oregon, Cows?, 6/2/95 C4 / Fire News/Prison Riot (Oregon) TV, Watermelon Pesticide, Fires, Rain Against Windows; audiocassette TDK D 60, undated; 092.0312 (Box Digitized Access Copies, File 092.0312)
    - -South America Argentina - Car etc.; audiocassette Citacrom CHF 90, undated; 092.0313 (Box Digitized Access Copies, File 092.0313)
    - - Storefront: -Dealers on Bowery Chrystie, Car Accident, 14 St., Union Square, Wash. Sq., etc., Chaco, Joe, Dealers on Rivington; audiocassette TDK D-C 60, undated; 092.0314 (Box Digitized Access Copies, File 092.0314)
    - -Side A Only, 25 min. approx., Times Square, 42 st., Midnight, Sat. Nite, 10-15 Min., Bowery Traffic, 3rd St. // Wojnarowicz/Street; audiocassette Maxell XLII 90, undated; 092.0315 (Box Digitized Access Copies, File 092.0315)
    - -Swaggart / Musak; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D 60, undated; 092.0316 (Box Digitized Access Copies, File 092.0316)
    - -Soundtape / NYC ambulance // Wojnarowicz: Soundtape; audiocassette (F-4-C) Sony HF 60, undated; 092.0321 (Box Digitized Access Copies, File 092.0321)
    - -Soundtape II USA / Hostage, Sing a long Stuff, Jerry Falwell Stuff: How to Raise a Family for Fun etc., Flood News, etc. // Soundtape II USA; audiocassette (F-4-C) Maxell LN 60, undated; 092.0305 (Box Digitized Access Copies, File 092.0305)
    - -"Crazy man sex house" and answering machine messages, audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D 60, undated; 092.0322 (Box Digitized Access Copies, File 092.0322)
  - Subseries B: Primary Audio Works, 150061
    - -1988 Journal Wojnarowicz / Journal 1988 Nov. Dec.; audiocassette TDK D 90, 150122 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0218)
    - -Act-Up Demonstration etc., June 1989; audiocassette (F-4B) Sony HF 120, 150121 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0219)
    - -Affair journal 3/81; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D-60, 1981; 150120 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0220)
    - -AIDS Vaccines, Gary Null Show, WBAI-5/18/90, NYC; audiocassette (F-4-A) BASF Ferro Extra I 90, 1990; 150119 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0221)
    - -American Dreamtime: NYC, 1984, by Doug Bressler and David Wojnarowicz; audiocassette (F-4-D) Maxell XLII-S 60, 092.0222; 150118 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0222, Box Digitized Access Copies, File fales_20111220_wojnarowicz_092_0222)
    - -American Dreamtime, David Wojnarowicz & Doug Bressler; 1/4" analog reel, 1984; 150117 (Case 092.0160)
    - -Breakdown Journal NYC- Jan.; audiocassette D-C 60, undated; 150116 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0223)
      Format: 1/8" audiocassette, Duration: 63 minutes
      Currently available.
    - -Cross country/ great dreams- 1989, Pt. 1; audiocassette (F-4B) Sony HF 60, 092.0224; 150115 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0224, Box Digitized Access Copies, File fales_20111220_wojnarowicz_092_0224)
    - -Cross country/ great dreams- 1989, Pt. 2; audiocassette (F-4B) Sony HF 60, 092.0225; 151538 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0225, Box Digitized Access Copies, File fales_20111220_wojnarowicz_092_0225)
    - -Cross country/ great dreams- 1989, Pt. 3; audiocassette (F-4B) Sony HF 60, 151539 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0226)
    - -David; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 90, undated; 092.0227; 150114 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0227, Box Digitized Access Copies, File fales_20111220_wojnarowicz_092_0227)
    - -David, John conversation, 12/31/80; audiocassette (F-4B) Scotch Dynarange, 1980; 150113 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0228)
    - -David Wojanrowicz queer song; audiocassette (F-4B) FUJI DR-I 90, undated; 092.0229; 150112 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0229, Box Digitized Access Copies, File fales_20111220_wojnarowicz_092_0229)
    - -David tape I, David tape II; audiocassette TDK D 90., undated; 150111 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0230)
    - -David Wojnarowicz, Friday, on censorship; microcassette (F-4-A) Sony MC 60, undated; 150110 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0231)
    - -David Wojnarowicz & Sylvere Lotringer, Pt. 1; audiocassette Sony EF 60, 1989; 150109 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0232)
    - -David Wojnarowicz & Sylvere Lotringer, Pt. 2; audiocassette Sony EF 60, 1989; 092.0233; 151540 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0233, Box Digitized Access Copies, File fales_20111220_wojnarowicz_092_0233)
    - -David Wojnarowicz & Sylvere Lotringer, Pt. 3; audiocassette Sony EF 60, 1989; 151541 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0234)
    - -Desire journal #1 of 2 / Affair journal; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D-C 60, undated; 092.0235; 150108 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0235, Box Digitized Access Copies, File fales_20110304_wojnarowicz_092_0235)
    - -Desire #2 of 2 (Last Version); audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 60, undated; 150107 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0236)
    - -Doug David, Storefront, Do not tape over this side; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D-C 60, undated; 150106 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0237)
    - -Success // Ending loneliness; audiocassette (F-4B) Sony CHF 90, undated; 150105 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0238)
    - -Hujar interview, tape 1; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 90, undated; 150104 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0239)
    - -Phil: Health Stuff // Interview: Mary Hayslip re: Montanna's death 4/9/90 / Phil, Richard last tape; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 90, 1990; 150103 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0240)
    - -Interview with Ruth Hirschman-7/23/90; audiocassette (F-4-A) KCRW 89.9, 1990; 150102 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0241)
    - -Side 1: Interview with Ruth Hirschman-7/23/90, Side 2: ARTS/LA Tongues of Flame-8/13/90; audiocassette (F-4-A) KCRW 89.9, 1990; 151542 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0242)
    - -Interview with Susan Wyett/Artists Space, NYC/60 min.; audiocassette TDK D 60, undated; 150101 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0243)
    - -Jesse; audiocassette (F-4B) Memorex MRX I 30, undated; 150100 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0244)
    - -John/David conversation 12/31/80; audiocassette (F-4B) Scotch Dynarange 90, 1980; 150099 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0245)
    - -Journal; audiocassette (F-4B) Sony EF 60, undated; 150098 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0246)
    - -Journal #2, 1988-89; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 60, 150097 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0247)
    - -Junk journal April 27-28, 1982, NYC // Jim Fourat/Junk Tape; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D-C 60, 150096 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0248)
    - -KCRW Radio interview with Ruth Hirschman; audiocassette TDK AV-D 120, 1990; 150095 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0249)
    - -Loneliness #2; audiocassette (F-4B) Sony CHF 90, undated; 150094 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0250)
    - -Hunke/Louis; audiocassette Certron LN 60, 151543 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0251)
    - -Some Cats Swing // Louis Cartwright tape 3, Finish up this side / Louis Cartwright 3TK4; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK SD-C 60, undated; 150093 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0252)
    - -Louis Cartwright tape 5 / Heavy Truck Drivin Poetry - "And a Happy New Year","Bologna la Influenza (Opera)", "Interrogation"; audiocassette Capitol 60, 151544 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0253)
    - -Louis last tape I / II; audiocassette (F-4B) Certron LN 60, undated; 150092 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0254)
    - -Louis last tape, Sept. 77 / Another Night at Columbia Side 2; audiocassette TDK D-C 90, 1977; 150091 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0255)
    - -Lung and Casandra Starke Interview // Lung, Cassandra, Parental Abuse Interview; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 90, undated; 150090 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0256)
    - -The Manhattan Transfer Body and Souls / Wojnarowicz Public Radio; audiocassette TDK D 90, undated; 150089 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0257)
    - -Paris-New York communications; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D - C60, undated; 150088 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0258)
    - -Phil Z/David W. (Connie) / Phil/David (1st tape); audiocassette (F-4B), undated; 150087 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0259)
    - -Ben Neill/Dis-Solution 2 // Journal / White House Press Schedule; audiocassette TDK D 90, 1986; 151694 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0260)
    - -Ming Ma Cantonese / Performance tape (Languages) // Performance tape / Languages; audiocassette (F-4-D) Sony HF 60, undated; 150086 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0261)
    - -Phil/David [2nd tape]; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK SA 60, undated; 150085 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0262)
    - -D.W.NJ.G.T. June 89 / (1) If I Had $ (2) Cuz I (3) Last Nite I Took A Man Home (4) Vision Piece (5) Goddess of Life + Death // Kostabi / Phil died; audiocassette Panasonic C 60, 1989; 150084 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0263)
    - -Zwickler Demo A. Space; microcassette (F-4-A) Realistic MC-60, undated; 150083 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0264)
    - -Project Inform, Pt. 1; audiocassette Sony HF 60, undated; 150082 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0265)
    - -Project Inform, Pt. 2; audiocassette Sony HF 60, undated; 151686 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0266)
    - -Project Inform, Pt. 3; audiocassette Sony HF 60, undated; 151687 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0267)
    - -Reading - Club 57; audiocassette (F-4-D) Scotch Dynarange 60, undated; 150081 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0268)
    - -Releasing Guilt; audiocassette (F-4-G) TDK D-C 90, undated; 150080 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0269)
    - -Richard Kern on Montanna 1990 (tape 1) // Richard Kern April 9 1990 RE: Montanna; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 90, 150079 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0270)
    - -Richard tape VII; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 90, undated; 150078 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0271)
    - -(May 16 1982) NYC Self Conversations, Peters Loft, (RE: Sex / J.P. / Confusions); audiocassette TDK D-C 60, 150077 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0272)
    - -Short Essay on Photographs for Madoka, NYC 84 3-5 minutes; audiocassette TDK D 60, 1984; 150076 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0273)
    - -Sophie on Montanna, Tape V; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 90, undated; 150075 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0274)
    - -Chosen to Stay + Fight; audiocassette (F-4-G) TDK D-C 60, undated; 150074 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0275)
    - -Steve #; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 60, undated; 150073 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0276)
    - -(Tape Journal) Clown laugh, use w/Doug // Recording #2 Steve Doughton, Philip Zimmerman, David W., Doug B. / Insane Laughter; audiocassette (F-4B) Maxell UD-XL II 60, undated; 150072 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0277)
    - -Tape Journal; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 60, undated; 150071 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0278)
    - -Tommy tape VI // Tommy -Montana [2] / Tommy (partial); audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 90, undated; 150070 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0279)
    - -Tommy Turner on Montanna 1990 / 1/2 used: Tommy/Richard phone call; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 90, 150069 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0280)
    - -Tongues of Flame Opening, 7/26 - 27, 90 Normal, IL- NPR Interview / Opening + Interview Blinderman / Wojnarowicz, Ina Jaffee NPR; audiocassette (F-4-A) KCRW 89.9, 1990; 150068 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0281)
    - -Traveling; audiocassette (F-4B) Capitol music tape 60 minutes, undated; 150067 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0282)
    - -Jan 1990 Panel Discussion w Paul Marcus, WBAI; audiocassette (F-4-A) TDK SA 90, 150066 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0283)
    - -WBAI Panel w Paul Marcus; audiocassette (F-4-A) TDK SA 90, undated; 150065 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0284)
    - -WBAI Panel; audiocassette (F-4-A) TDK D 60, undated; 150064 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0285)
    - -ITSOFOMO Copy; audiocassette 3M R120 DAT, undated; 150063 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0286)
    - -Jan Bruce Audio Poetry; audiocassette Maxell UR 90, undated; 150062 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0287)
    - -ITSOFOMO rough mix; audiocassette TDK SA 60, undated; 151695 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0288)
    - -ITSOFOMO Final Mix / Meat Bloody Memory War; audiocassette Maxell XL-II 100, 1991; 151696 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0289)
  - Subseries C: Sound Materials, 150025
    - -Broken piano/musak/jack hammer/Rev. Swaggart Mix; audiocassette TDK D 60, undated; 150060 (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0290)
    - -Bum Crash, Ship Horn, [Speed], Clocks, Firing Range, Chose to Stay & Fight; audiocassette (F-4-C) Ampex 60, undated; 150059 (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0291)
    - -Car crash; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK EC 1, undated; 150058 (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0292)
      TDK Endless EC1 cassette tape. The format is designed to loop endlessly and requires specialized equipment to play back.
    - -Fashion chit-chat, Queer dinner / Ready on the Right - Roll Back for El Salvadore Song; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D-C 60, undated; 150057 (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0293)
    - -Gunfire Brian's song, Brian's song / Bum crash, Traffic report, Louis session 2; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D-C 90, undated; 150056 (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0294)
    - -Hunger, Siren Pulse Beat, Buzzer, Surf / Crickets, Birds, Pool, Road Movie, Alcholism, Hold-up Tape [+] 10 Second; audiocassette TDK D-C 60, undated; 150055 (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0295)
    - -Windshield Wipers, [Buvsisles], Hut; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D-C 60, undated; 150054 (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0296)
    - -KIDS; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D 120, undated; 150053 (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0297)
    - -Mexico soundtrack; audiocassette (F-2) Maxell XLII 90, undated; 150052 (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0361)
    - -PRISON SEX, Sex Movie Music/Prison: Drums; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D 60, undated; 150051 (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0298)
    - -Queer riot fragments; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D 90, undated; 150050 (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0299)
    - -Reagan; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK EC 1, undated; 150049 (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0300)
    - -Sounds: Reagan Shooting / Down & Out in Paris & London, [Asteroids] - Galaxian; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D-C 60, undated; 150048 (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0301)
    - -Reagan/various stations; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK EC 3, undated; 150047 (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0302)
    - -Recorder/Harmonica; audiocassette Realistic Supertape HD-90., undated; 150046 (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0303)
    - **Missing**-Recording session w/ Doug Bressler 4/18 (no year given); 1/4" audiotape (F-3), undated; 150045 (Box 18, Folder no number)
    - -Garbage Truck in 14 St. Meat Market / Sex Movies; audiocassette TDK D 60, undated; 150044 (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0304)
    - -Soundtape II USA / Hostage, Sing a long Stuff, Jerry Falwell Stuff: How to Raise a Family for Fun etc., Flood News, etc. // Soundtape II USA; audiocassette (F-4-C) Maxell LN 60, undated; 150043 (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0305)
    - -Soundtape USA #3 / Plane Taking off N. Mexico, Spanish Movie (Black Cat Appears), Bed Rock City (Dino Barking), Water, etc.; audiocassette (F-4-C) Maxell LN 60, undated; 150042 (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0306)